[Music]
you love beauty products
oh you were interested in working at
ulta
you clicked the right video at the right
time
because i was waiting for you at the
[Music]
adult
beauties it's a caribbean cutie back
with something different today
so today i would actually be telling you
the benefits
of working at ulta i'm just going to be
discussing most of the
freebies that you get working at ulta
let's just start off by saying
this is a medium-sized bag and this is a
filled with products three
products so
i just have to admit this wig i love
this oh my gosh
look at my elbow i'm dealing with some
eczema right now so don't be talking
about me
at least saying ashley though so i'm
gonna just get right
into this video i just dumped my
freebies in here
so this is the first time i'm actually
digging in this bag for the first time
in a
while because the gifts just keep coming
okay so the first thing we got is this
flexible hold hairspray by bumble and
bumble
a lot of these brands i never knew about
until working at ulta
this is certainly one of them i don't
know what it is
but i'll be wearing wigs companies be
sending me wigs like this one
shout out to glory lace wig i love
this hair so never know these stuff
don't come in handy
and the next one oh
two of the same thing all right
works fine for me and i'm not going in
any particular type of order
like hair skincare or anything like that
i'm just
picking it out this one is by it
cosmetics
it's a oil free foundation i have to try
it um
shout out to kat she always take good
care of me she's one of the vendors
for it cosmetics we have vendors come
through every week
that try to sell a number of products so
she always tells me like you know z if
you help me sell this amount of products
i have a foundation for you or i'm gonna
give you you know i love cat but
yeah she takes care of me so free matte
foundation i also got this
setting spray full size setting spray
these are full size items these are not
little samples
i mean i have some samples in here too
but the for the most part i have full
size items
this is a full size setting spray by it
cosmetics
and i can't wait to use it because you
got hyaluronic acid in it coconut water
aloe vera extract all the good stuff and
it smell like a beach
like it's not like coconut
you know what
that smells so good this setting spray
you can actually use it even when you're
not wearing makeup
this one is by sunday riley
another brand that i had no idea about
before working at ulta
this is a prestige brand oh by the way i
might as well just tell you up my
position so i am a prestige
beauty advisor they put me in prestige
without even meaning
really knowing what that was the story
split up into two sections
drugstore brands and prestige brands
which consists of the
urban decays the tarte um
matte cosmetics all the high-end brands
so i guess she saw the quality of my
makeup i was like
yeah honestly my comfort zone was in the
drugstore products
so i would always take customers over
there
and my gm was like we gotta get you from
off
that side of the store you need to stay
over here
i was like oh my gosh so now you know
i'm getting more used to the products
and especially them giving me free
products it helps me try the product so
i'm not lying to customers i'm like oh
yeah that really works really well
and have no idea how it works like i
actually know how it works like
this right here this was also a freebie
this is by urban decay
this is the all nighter setting spring
and the market price for this is thirty
dollars
forty dollars actually no
thirty three dollars full size and i get
this for free
like i got it for free so after using
this
i cannot go back to nyx i can't go back
to nyx setting spray like i just can't
like
it's like going back to craft cheese
after trying cracker barrel
you know yeah that's the only way i can
explain it
so yeah this is my favorite this is my
go-to
anyway back to sunday riley this is
called good jeans and it had it's a
lactic acid treatment
so pretty much this works like pacman
once you put it on your skin it eats
away at the dead skin
you could pretty much use this at night
or some people put it on before they put
on their makeup
for me i would put it on at night i
haven't used it yet i just got it the
other day
and then we got some sample sizes
by first aid beauty this is the ultra
repair
face moisturizer i also got this from
the first aid beauty
vendor that came in so they come in
sometimes they come in with a whole lot
of samples and they're like here you go
we call it gratis so they'll be like i
got some gratis for you today and then
they'll just
you know hand it off to you or whatever
this is by dermalogica
another prestige brand this is the hydro
mask exfoliant so i'm gonna try this
because i'm into skincare now i mean i
always trying to find what works for my
skin so i was really appreciative for
this
this is the mario badescu aha
botanical body soap this is also a
sample size
and i got the anastasia
beverly hills loose setting powder
now the color is translucent i'm not
really feeling it because i'm black
and this thing is white
the thing white white white look
i don't even know how to use this it's
like powder but i'm gonna see
how to use it or i don't know
i have to give it to my sister-in-law
somebody because somebody likes skin
because sis i'm black
i don't know i gotta do it but i
appreciate the free gift oh you got
something else by bumble and bumble this
is the thickening dryspun texture spray
creates instant volume and holds airy
texture all day okay
um what do we have here
laura marcier blurring
silicone free pure canvas primer
this is what it looks like never used it
before
i'm curious i'd like a dewy finish even
though somehow i always end up with a
mat
this is what it looks like let me see
it doesn't have a smell oh
it does dry matte
wow yeah yeah that mm-hmm
if you feel it you know
sis
you're not about to be oily with this i
could tell you that much like
this is it you oily this is it
this is it and i actually have two of
those
imagine one of them i think i got from
so basically you could get free gifts
when you
do like if you do your trainings on time
we have training that will teach us you
know train us on different products in
the store
or any new brands that we may be
launching different stuff like that
if you do the trainings then you get
gratis
or sometimes the brand will give the
store a goal
of how many products or a number of
items to sell
and if we make that goal then all the
employees get a
free for example a free primer
so i ended up with two because one time
i think i got it from
training doing my training on time and
then the second time we made goal
and then i got a second one so
hey i never running low on primer
another sample by soap and glory i
always wanted to try this so
i can't wait to do that and you better
glue body butter by soap and glory
the dermalogica
invisible physical defense
sunscreen and actually use this the
other day and it really does
it doesn't have that white cast so i can
vouch for that for
my black folks it has spf 30 in it
so you know it's about to protect pretty
your skin but better foundation by it
cosmetics
i actually use this now i have it on my
face right now
i honestly thought if cosmetics were
like a old people brand
matter of fact how old white people
brand but
they let me sample these two in that
sample this is the full size
uh you know my girl cat gave me this and
a match full coverage everything like i
thought it just wasn't gonna work for
my skin my black skin tone i didn't
thought it was going to be full coverage
it's not full full coverage but it is
buildable
i really really like it i'd be telling
people if you're looking for
skin care plus a good foundation i would
go for
this brand i like it i think there's
hyaluronic acid in this foundation as
well
so if you are oily you need probably
this laura mercier
matte primer to balance out this because
it is very hydrating but i'm not very
oily so i could afford to use this
urban decay volumizing mascara and this
is
a perversion this is a waterproof kind
the box feels so cool the water drops
are 3d
full size free also
the nars climax volumizing mascara
free full size and this bottle is
actually cool too
it looks really nice and you know with
all these products i should be pretty
generous and give it to people
you know but you know some people have
different gifts the gift of teaching
the gift of giving the gift of all kind
of gifts you can look it up in the bible
giving is not one of mine i'm like
fine
[Music]
but eventually i'm not going to use all
of this so i don't have to start to give
it
this is by botanic's brand a skincare
line
this is mass we call drugstore products
mask
so this is mass skin care it's a
nourishing
facial oil for all skin types i like it
i use it
you know give you a nice little healthy
glow and i also got the face
primer long wear foundation grip by
urban decay
this is what this looks like it doesn't
say matte
but it does leave your face matte so
pretty much
if you use something like this then you
just use a hydrating
setting spray and it should balance
everything out
dry bar the chaser high shine finishing
cream
i've used this in one of my wigs by
premium lace wig
it really works it makes it really soft
it could rejuvenate a dry
wig because mine would dry and this
made it look good as new and it smells
really good
bare minerals original foundation
and this actually have spf in it as well
not my favorite sorry but
not my favorite i just don't i'm i'm a
liquid type of girl and this powder
is weird to me not knocking the brand
somebody else may like it and it's a
healthy it's a good brand
it's cruelty free it doesn't have all
kind of harmful stuff in it
so you could try it out i just didn't
like it plus it was too dark for me it
made me look
weird
some more freebies by botanics
cosmetics and soap and glory
and oh number seven the brand number
seven
it's a line correcting um probably get
it to my mom because
i don't have lines i'm 25
confidence in a cleanser by it cosmetics
it cut
come through should sponsor me and i
actually used it and it was
really really good i like how it felt
how the bare minerals look
it comes like this
and then it look like that
and then you're supposed to technically
like put
it in the cover and then you take
a brush and you warm it up a little bit
and then you
put it on your face and i got
two of those
not my style this i got by urban decay
after glow eight hour powder blush
this is actually purple though even
though it's a blush it's purple
urban decay their brand excites me
like look at this this is bad
bleep look at her this is so
cute this is what it looks like on the
inside
i actually got this when i went to a
off-site
training and they were training you
strictly on urban decay products and i
loved it like i just i like urban decay
i love the brand
i have this anastasia eye primer
so i guess you use this before um
eyeshadow
so this is what it looks like let me see
the color
okay i can walk with that
that's what it looks like
it is bright
so we not too long ago launched kat von
d
well i think it's called kvd now and
we had a goal of how many i couldn't
remember what we had to sell but
whatever it was
we sold it and everyone got a
free go big or go home volumizing
mascara
look at that so how many mascaras is i
don't have look at her
i'm good to go this is the version
waterproof fine point
eye pen and i actually use this one
where is it this is what it looks like
the fine point and i like it whenever
you're
storing it i would say just store it
upside down so the ink could
run to the point it works good
liquid eyeliner by anastasia
and this is also really good i've used
this one
yep this one is more it has a shiny
finish i think the waterproof one by
urban decay has more of a
matte finish just a little tip just in
case i wanted to know that
this is a prestige brand this is by
origins
clear improvement active charcoal mask
the market price for this probably cost
i don't even know this is this is
expensive stuff
so i'm so grateful to have this for free
kvd tattoo liner how about
a liner oh my gosh this is crazy laura
mercier
caviar stick eye color so it's like a
cream eyeshadow
as a lipstick or a lip gloss or
something to be honest
i don't use cream eyeshadow this is the
color it looks
how pretty is that imaginary lips
this is just a sample of mac foundation
anastasia beverly hills brow wiz i
didn't even know i had this
wait all the broadway's yet not my
favorite i don't really like how skinny
the point is
i like something a little thicker
because this is going to take me forever
but yeah that that costs
24 imagine and i get it for free
i'm gonna keep reminding y'all because
this is crazy
um this is the anastasia beverly hills
dipbrow gel which is what i use now
mind you i want to stick to drugstore
products for god knows how long no
i use expensive stuff on my face i use
this on my brows now
it's so easy and it helps me finish my
brows a lot faster
so you just dip it and you just brush it
onto the
hair love it love it these are some
sample sizes
the facial radiance pads by
first aid beauty it helps exfoliate tone
and brightening and it's alcohol
free again expensive
prestige brand exuviance
prestige brand all of these are like uh
what is it
pure retinol so is like a peeling
some type of peel i'm scared to use it
to be honest but i'm gonna use it
more mario badescu botanical body soap
it cosmetics confidence in a cream
for the grand finale
the latest skincare line that we
launched is by
beakman1802 i think that's why you say
uh beekman for sure everything by this
brand is made i'm trying to figure out
my english how to wear this stuff
everything by this brand
is created by
were created
the owners of this brand i think owns a
farm somewhere and they use the goat
milk to
create beauty products so this is what
it looks like
for all skin types and everyone i use it
really it has good reviews they always
say that
it leaves their skin feeling really
moisturized these are all
full-size products in here so cool
and i think it's pretty neat it says
effective clean ingredients
let your skin drink it in and this
is the deep cleanse milk wash
exfoliating jelly cleanser this is the
milk drops
probiotic ceramide serum so this is the
cleanse treat and moisturize
the package it is so neat like i've
never seen anything
like it i love it so you press this down
and then it comes through the top
might as well test it out let me see
what i smell like
it smell like milk it's rich though
yeah it smell like milk that's that's a
little weird to me smell like you like
when you're breastfeeding a child
literally smell like milk but it's very
very
rich and it comes in this
cute little keepsake bag like i've
actually used this for
makeup when i traveling or something so
you put this
in here and that's how you store it i
can't wait to try i
i'm willing to try it out um but that's
all i
have like i have so many stuff by ulta
for free so
all in all if you love beauty products
i would consider working outside you
have nothing to lose working on ulta
like
i mean hopefully you could up your pay
rate a little bit
but um other than that even if it's just
a part-time job so you
reap the benefits of getting the beauty
products for free then do that
but i enjoy working for ulta because
they sometimes i cook if i stay in the
house all the time i get lazy i don't
feel like putting on makeup but when i
go to work
i'll be like oh my gosh i want to try it
i want to try it i want to try it i want
to try it out then i end up just
going home and playing around with
makeup and you know so
that's all i'm going to wrap this video
up all in all go and get your
application and apply to ulta
today tell them
the youtuber that lives in fort worth
sent you my name is zazelle
so i hope they put me on for something
so yeah thank you guys for stopping by
make sure to like comment and subscribe
to my channel
share this video if you know somebody
that was considering working for
ulta or loves beauty products i would
enjoy a video like this
follow my instagram and i am zazelle
and just thank y'all for who already is
subscribed to my channel thank you for
sticking this out with me
and being with me from the start love
y'all
love you beauties
so guys these are some additional
products i accumulated
after recording this video just look
at all the goodies
hmm
you were interested in working at ulta